//faq section
export const general = [
    { id: 0,
      title: "General",
      subtitle: "Understand the basics of LindaPay's secure digital payment solution",
     },
     { id: 1,
        question: "What is LindaPay?",
        answer: "LindaPay is a digital escrow solution designed to enhance trust and security in digital transactions. It offers escrow services that protect both buyers and sellers.",
       },
       { id: 2,
        question: "How does LindaPay work?",
        answer: "LindaPay acts as a trusted intermediary, ecuring funds until both parties confirm that the transaction terms are met.",
       },
       { id: 3,
        question: "How is my money secured?",
        answer: "All LindaPay payments are processed with PCI/DSS Certified payment processors and all funds are safely held in a CBN-Licensed Deposit Money Bank.",
       },
     
];
export const pricing = [
    { id: 0,
      title: "Pricing",
      subtitle: "Understand the transparent and flexible transaction fee structure of LindaPay's services.",
     },
     { id: 1,
        question: "How much does LindaPay charge for its services?",
        answer: "LindaPay charges a transparent fee of 2% + ksh100 of the transaction amount. This fee can be paid by either the buyer or the seller, or it can be split between both parties.",
       },
       { id: 2,
        question: "Are there any additional fees?",
        answer: "No, the 2% + ksh100 transaction fee covers the cost of using LindaPay's services. There are no hidden charges or extra fees.",
       },
       { id: 3,
        question: "What is the minimum and maximum transaction amount?",
        answer: "The minimum transaction amount is â‚¦1,000, and there is no maximum limit.",
       },
       { id: 4,
        question: "Who pays for the transaction fee?",
        answer: "The transaction fee of 2% + ksh100 is paid by either the buyer or the seller, or it can be split between both parties based on the mutual agreement reached during the transaction.",
       }
     
];
export const privacy = [
    { id: 0,
      title: "Privacy",
      subtitle: "Understand how LindaPay protects your privacy and data.",
     },
     { id: 1,
        question: "Is my personal information safe with LindaPay?",
        answer: "Yes, we take privacy seriously. We adhere to strict security measures, including SSL certificate, data encryption and protection protocols and our business entity is in full compliance with the Kenyan Data Protection Regulations (NDPR).",
       },
       { id: 2,
        question: "Does LindaPay share my data with third parties?",
        answer: " No, LindaPay does not share your data with any third parties. LindaPay is in full compliance with the Kenya Data Protection Regulations.",
       }
     
];

export const dispute = [
    { id: 0,
      title: "Dispute Resolution",
      subtitle: "Learn about how LindaPay resolves transaction disputes.",
     },
     { id: 1,
        question: "What happens if a dispute arises during a transaction?",
        answer: " In case of a dispute, LindaPay provides a seamless dispute resolution process. Our team helps mediate and resolve issues to ensure a fair outcome for both parties.",
       },
       { id: 2,
        question: "How long does the dispute resolution procedure take?",
        answer: "The duration of the dispute resolution process depends on the complexity of the issue. However, LindaPay aims to address and resolve disputes in a timely manner.",
       }
     
];